export const mathChallenges = [
    { id: 1, question: '5 + 7 = ?', options: ['12', '10', '11'], answer: '12' },
    { id: 2, question: '12 - 5 = ?', options: ['7', '6', '8'], answer: '7' },
    { id: 3, question: '3 + 8 = ?', options: ['10', '11', '12'], answer: '11' },
    { id: 4, question: '10 - 4 = ?', options: ['6', '5', '7'], answer: '6' },
    { id: 5, question: '2 + 3 + 4 = ?', options: ['8', '9', '7'], answer: '9' },
    { id: 6, question: '15 - 7 = ?', options: ['7', '8', '9'], answer: '8' },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: '4 + 5 + 6 = ?',
        options: ['14', '15', '16'],
        answer: '15',
    },
    { id: 8, question: '8 - 3 + 2 = ?', options: ['7', '8', '6'], answer: '7' },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: '5 + 5 + 5 = ?',
        options: ['15', '14', '13'],
        answer: '15',
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: '9 - 4 + 3 = ?',
        options: ['8', '9', '7'],
        answer: '8',
    },
    // add more for total 30+ challenges
]
